[
  {
    "questionText": "Which is the most popular JavaScript framework?",
    "answers": ["Angular", "React", "Svelte", "Vue"],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
    "pausedOn": 2
  },
  {
    "questionText": "When will an effect run if it doesn't have a dependency array?",
    "answers": [
      "Only when the component mounts",
      "Only when the component unmounts",
      "The first time the component re-renders",
      "Each time the component is re-rendered"
    ],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
    "pausedOn": 5
  },
  {
    "questionText": "What's the fundamental building block of React apps?",
    "answers": ["Components", "Blocks", "Elements", "Effects"],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
    "pausedOn": 15
  },
  {
    "questionText": "What's the name of the syntax we use to describe the UI in React components?",
    "answers": ["FBJ", "Babel", "JSX", "ES2015"],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
    "pausedOn": 20
  },
  {
    "questionText": "How does data flow naturally in React apps?",
    "answers": [
      "From parents to children",
      "From children to parents",
      "Both ways",
      "The developers decides"
    ],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
    "pausedOn": 25
  },
  {
    "questionText": "How to pass data into a child component?",
    "answers": ["State", "Props", "PropTypes", "Parameters"],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
    "pausedOn": 30
  },
  {
    "questionText": "When to use derived state?",
    "answers": [
      "Whenever the state should not trigger a re-render",
      "Whenever the state can be synchronized with an effect",
      "Whenever the state should be accessible to all components",
      "Whenever the state can be computed from another state variable"
    ],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
    "pausedOn": 35
  },
  {
    "questionText": "What triggers a UI re-render in React?",
    "answers": [
      "Running an effect",
      "Passing props",
      "Updating state",
      "Adding event listeners to DOM elements"
    ],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
    "pausedOn": 40
  },
  {
    "questionText": "When do we directly \"touch\" the DOM in React?",
    "answers": [
      "When we need to listen to an event",
      "When we need to change the UI",
      "When we need to add styles",
      "Almost never"
    ],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
    "pausedOn": 50
  },
  {
    "questionText": "In what situation do we use a callback to update state?",
    "answers": [
      "When updating the state will be slow",
      "When the updated state is very data-intensive",
      "When the state update should happen faster",
      "When the new state depends on the previous state"
    ],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
    "pausedOn": 55
  },
  {
    "questionText": "If we pass a function to useState, when will that function be called?",
    "answers": [
      "On each re-render",
      "Each time we update the state",
      "Only on the initial render",
      "The first time we update the state"
    ],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
    "pausedOn": 60
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Which hook to use for an API request on the component's initial render?",
    "answers": ["useState", "useEffect", "useRef", "useReducer"],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
    "pausedOn": 65
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Which variables should go into the useEffect dependency array?",
    "answers": [
      "Usually none",
      "All our state variables",
      "All state and props referenced in the effect",
      "All variables needed for clean up"
    ],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
    "pausedOn": 70
  },
  {
    "questionText": "An effect will always run on the initial render.",
    "answers": [
      "True",
      "It depends on the dependency array",
      "False",
      "In depends on the code in the effect"
    ],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
    "pausedOn": 75
  },
  {
    "questionText": "When will an effect run if it doesn't have a dependency array?",
    "answers": [
      "Only when the component mounts",
      "Only when the component unmounts",
      "The first time the component re-renders",
      "Each time the component is re-rendered"
    ],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
    "pausedOn": 80
  }
]
